The Witch Hat World Tree is one of the
Aradia Kingdom's tourist hot spots.
It is a thousand years old
and stands 900 meters tall.
Beyond the tunnel is...
the Royal Diana Academy of Magic.
Diana was established roughly a thousand
years ago by the founding witch, Selene.
Between its middle school and high school
divisions, it has over 600 students.
Wow, wow!
I'm actually at Diana!
Everything about this place is so pretty!
Everyone's so elegant and distinguished.
No wonder, given this
school's so prestigious!
And the uniforms are so cute.
Wait, I'm wearing the same one!
Calm down.
Your stupid is showing.
Master!
Call me Professor Claude.
Remember, no one can know
that you're my apprentice.
Sure, sure.
So is it a secret that you transform
into a cute little kitty, too?
Obviously!
Then please be careful not to use up
your magic and turn back into a cat.
I don't like it either, you know.
You made me kiss your
butt this morning, too.
It's super embarrassing,
even knowing that it's
so that you can get back
to your human form.
Does it bother you?
Of course it does!
It's embarrassing for me, too, and I
feel bad making you do that for me.
But I couldn't teach as a cat, could I?
W-Well, yeah...
In any case, we ought to cooperate.
Our goal is the same: to make
you a first-class magician.
I know, but...
Let us work together
toward our common dream!
I feel like I'm being
hoodwinked by a bad man.
Also, I'll talk to the principal
about your coven. Don't worry.
My coven?
You don't know what that is?
You should if you're
going to a magic school.
Well, I was going to
a normal school before.
A coven is...
Mr. Sirius.
Already making friends with your
students? Impressive as always.
It's been a while, Principal Jeanne.
Now he's acting proper!
Also, the principal's so young!
The school's abuzz with
word of your return.
Abuzz, huh?
Yes.
Though it's mostly people
badmouthing you.
The principal's a sadist!
That hurts to hear.
I don't want to cause any
confusion among the students.
May I ask you to wait in my office
until the covens are announced?
I just happened to have an
inquiry regarding the covens.
Oh, what might it be?
I can't wait to hear.
I'll figure it out with her.
Stay out of trouble.
No, you!
Well, let's go.
I wonder if those two are friends.
Where the hell did you
wander off to for two years?
Don't you run away this time,
my dumbass apprentice.
Well, well, Master Jeanne.
You're just as beautiful
as you were two years ago.
What kind of magic is that?
You'd best watch your tone.
I only gave you your job back
out of the kindness of my heart.
I'm grateful for that.
Wait, maybe they aren't.
Shoot, I didn't get to
find out what a coven was.
What do I do now?
Somebody!
Is anyone there?!
How did this even happen?!
I...
I slipped and fell and
ended up in the wall!
Is that a thing?!
Could you please pull me out?
Okay, I guess...
Here I go.
One, two...
You won't come out!
My breasts are stuck!
Thanks.
You're my savior.
A sexy lady appears!
I'm Io Taurus.
And you?
I'm Spica Virgo, a first-year.
You're in my year!
Nice to meet you, Spica!
She's in my year?
My... year?
I hope we're in the same coven.
Um, so... what's a coven?
I came from a normal school,
so I don't really know.
A coven is your class.
A coven at Diana consists of
twelve students and a teacher.
They spend three years studying,
eating, and living together.
Three whole years?
Who you end up with is
really important, then.
It is.
So when Master said he'd
take care of my coven,
he meant he'd put me in his coven.
I hope I'm with nice people.
I've been at Diana since middle school.
Everyone here is kind and diligent.
I guess, huh? This school's prestigious.
Exactly.
Our covens should be announced soon.
Wanna go check the bulletin boards?
Okay.
Sorry!
Hey...
Are you hurt? Let me get a good look.
Huh?! N-No, I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
If someone as beautiful
as you were to be hurt...
B-Beautiful?!
Beautiful? Aw...
Am I?
Hi there.
You're as beautiful as a goddess, too.
I'm Libra. Nice to meet you.
He's just a horndog!
Oh, let's speak again later.
Ma'am, you dropped your handkerchief.
No, she didn't.
What's wrong with him?
Is he a pick-up artist?
Libra...
I heard he's the vice principal's son.
That scary-looking vice principal?
Is this school okay?
You there, beautiful miss.
Sorry, I lied about your handkerchief.
I just wanted to talk to you.
Should we stop him?
Oh, it's fine.
I've known these people
since middle school.
That girl...
I mean, Castor's a boy.
Who the hell are you calling "miss"?
I'm gonna smash your head in.
You're right!
I just realized he's wearing pants.
How did I get it wrong?
That's odd.
Sorry, looks like I made a mistake.
Nope. I'm making you pay.
Are you really that upset just
because I thought you were a girl?
That's not it!
I'm pissed that you touched
me with your filthy hands.
I'll kill you, you manslut.
What are you, a clean freak?
How could you call me dirty? That hurts.
I think I'll have you apologize.
Wait, you two!
You there, no fighting.
Who's she?
Fighting is bad.
You'll draw everyone's attention.
And no one takes the spotlight from me!
Holy crap, her body!
Well, well, if it isn't the Regulus lady.
Why make your entrance from a chandelier?
A foolish question.
To draw attention!
She sounds dumb!
You're in my way.
Get lost, meathead lady.
If you insist on fighting,
I'll have to stop you by force.
I can't stand brutes.
I wonder what we're having for lunch.
I thought Diana was
full of diligent students!
This isn't what I was promised!
Libra Magic: Eye of Themis.
The hell are you closing your eyes for?!
I don't need my eyes open
to dodge your attacks.
Stuff it.
Gemini Magic: Mirror Augment!
Save your bragging for after you've won.
Violence is so barbaric!
I appreciate the warning.
Someone, get a teacher!
How dare you show off without me?
Leo Magic: Lion Queen!
If you really want to fight...
I'll be happy to take you on.
I don't mind an invitation
from a beautiful lady,
but I'll pass this time.
I need to keep my distance from these
people for the next three years.
Are you okay?!
I'm totally fine.
I'm a tough girl.
You have a bump on your head!
What have you done to my savior?!
Now I'm angry!
Io...
Taurus Magic...
Gugalanna!
Please stop fighting!
Holy crap, that's so showy!
I'm jealous!
The women here are all freaks.
Bigger is better, right?
Io, your behind!
You're showing!
I'm sorry!
Ow!
Incoming dump truck!
Good grief.
You shouldn't be running wild at school.
M-Master—
Professor Claude!
Why the hell are you here?!
Why? To collect you, of course.
Castor Gemini, Astraea Libra,
Wow, I'm in the air! This is fun!
Leo Regulus, Io Taurus, Spica Virgo...
You're now in the Claude Coven.
You're my students.
I'm in the same coven as these people?!
How am I going to get through
the next three years?!
Claude, I understand your situation.
You're my former apprentice,
so I'll let you return.
I'll even let you have
Spica in your coven.
But the public won't accept it so easily.
True or not, the rumor that you fled
has the students suspicious of you.
You're no longer in the
same position as before.
So, in order to dispel their
doubts, I'll give you a test.
A test?
I've chosen students with high
potential for your Claude Coven.
But they're each a little troublesome.
You'll bring these twelve
students together.
Come on, Ewe, wake up. The teacher's here.
I feel like something fantastic
is about to happen.
Everyone looks so goofy.
Chiron, you shouldn't say that.
Waste of time.
Wow, I'm in Spica's coven. Hilarious.
You are to make sure everyone
graduates. No dropouts.
I'll have you leave if you don't succeed.
To think I'm back at this podium...
Very well.
I'll take care of all of them.
This is the beginning
of my new teaching life.
Huh? Where's the teacher?
So cute!
It's a cat.
Why is it here?
You're kidding me.
Looks like I used up all my
magic levitating that big body.
I told you to be careful!
Spica?
Cure my curse again, please?
No!
Weird chick.
Claude Coven, day one.
Spica Virgo flees.
Due to Mr. Claude's absence,
class is canceled.
Spica, it's morning.
Wake up.
Lemme sleep a little longer.
Okay.
I'll take you to school.
I'll get up!
I'll get up! Just let me down!
I'm sorry!
Morning.
Morning, Dorm Mother.
Good morning.
So you were the ones making
a racket this morning.
Give it back, Ewe!
Chiron, eat your peppers.
You spoiled my elegant tea time.
Shut up! You're not my mom!
Oh, sorry.
I'm glad you understand.
No cup?!
What happened to your elegance?!
There's something I have to do every
morning while the others have breakfast.
It all smells great!
What should I have?
You're late!
Is that how you ask someone for help?
I can't stand kissing you every morning!
Isn't there anything you can do?
What we know right now is...
The moment I use any
serious magic, I become a cat.
And by day's end, your Rebirth Magic
wears off, making me turn back into a cat.
Tsundere...
And you can only use
your magic once a day.
I need to sleep to
replenish my magic power.
I hate living like this.
I'll need you to become a first-class
magician by the time you graduate.
How can I do that?
FOURTH-CLASS
EARN A MAGICIAN CERTIFICATE HERE
Qualify for first class in the annual
rating exam at the royal palace.
THIRD-CLASS
Only 0.005% of magicians make it.
Only one person from Diana has ever
made it, even as prestigious as it is.
SECOND-CLASS
FIRST-CLASS
0.005% OF MAGICIANS
That's so slim! That person
must have been amazing!
That was me.
Damn it! I complimented him by accident!
In any case, over the next three years,
your aim is to become the
top student in your year.
Top student?!
You aren't going to make it
to first-class otherwise.
And you'll be expelled if your
grades fall behind. Be careful.
Per Diana policy, the bottom 10%
gets kicked out every year.
Don't get too cocky.
Okay.
Let's go to school.
Good morning, Dorm Mother.
You animal!
I mean, good morning, Mr. Claude!
Clandestine meetings in the morning...
Indecent relationship between
teacher and student...
This is a scandal!
Expulsion? There's no way
that'll happen to me.
I can't wait for my new school life!
Gacrux, the north school wing.
Here, students join with
those from other covens
Two masses are pulled toward
each other with a strength
to take classes in fundamental
subjects such as astronomy.
inversely proportionate to
the square of their distance.
The teacher's so fast! I can't keep up!
This is called the law
of universal gravitation.
The strength of this
gravity is denoted by F,
This girl next to me is sound asleep!
the masses of each object are
denoted by M and m respectively,
Hey, you should wake up.
and the distance is represented
by r in an equation.
The teacher's glaring!
Wake up!
Spica Virgo! No chit-chat!
Me?!
Tell me the equation for
universal gravitation!
I explained it just now.
If you were listening, you should know!
Help me!
F = GMm/r².
Correct, Ewe Aries.
Remember that, Spica Virgo!
Y-Yes, sir.
I wasn't expecting that.
You're really smart, aren't you?
She's asleep again!
She answered it without even being awake.
Meanwhile, I can't keep up at all!
Am I actually stupid?
In my class, I teach practical magic.
Today, we'll be assessing your abilities
by having you capture the most
lophorns within 30 minutes.
They may look cute,
but they're destructive animals.
Normal people have a
hard time catching them,
but my capable Diana students
ought to have no trouble.
I'm sure we won't have any slowpokes
who can't catch a single one.
That's some brutal pressure!
Begin!
Spica, are you sure you can catch them?
Have you forgotten how beautifully
I caught that golem?
A few bunnies aren't going
to be a problem!
I'm aiming for the top!
Virgo Magic: Anima!
No way! It's so fast!
I can't even touch it!
Lophorns use their horns
to detect magic power.
They run away the moment they
sense even a little magic.
Let's see how they deal with them.
What a waste of time...
Scorpio Magic: Fog Scorpion.
I've paralyzed you for a bit.
Blame the teacher, not me.
She released a paralyzing toxin.
Not bad.
There's no way they can get away,
even if they can detect it.
But the collateral damage is a problem.
Cancer Magic: Fulad Qafas!
They're so cute.
Wow.
One fell swoop.
I have to use Anima over a wide area...
No, they'll get away while
I'm waiting to activate it.
Expulsion.
I have to hurry.
Good work.
Now for the results.
In first place: Aria Aquarius,
who caught ten.
Easy.
In last place: Spica Virgo with zero.
I got headbutted by a lophorn,
and when I came to, it was over.
Well, that was too bad, Spica!
The hell are you doing?!
Have you no sense, either?!
We'll have remedial lessons after school.
You're going to get expelled at this rate!
Do you understand?
Yes.
What do I do?
It's my first day, and I'm
already falling behind.
I thought I could do a little better.
Never mind being top of my year...
What if I really get expelled?
You're late.
You're slow because you stare at
the ground and drag your feet.
Did you call me here to scold me?
We could have done remedial
lessons in your office.
What is this place?
An observatory.
Diana has several of them.
Huh.
You can even use them like this.
I cast visualization and levitation
magic on the entire room.
They let you create a virtual
recreation of space.
The stars are so pretty!
That's Deneb.
Altair.
Vega.
That big, blueish-white one is Spica.
I know.
That's the one with my name.
Spica may look like one star,
but it's actually two stars spinning
so rapidly that they look like one.
What is this, an astronomy class?
The light they produce is said to
be 20,000 times that of the Sun.
Wow.
The point is, well, even if one can
only produce so much light,
two together can produce incredible power.
Are you trying to cheer me up?
Are you telling me I'll be all
right because I'm not alone?
What?!
Obviously not!
I feel better after laughing.
And what's so funny? Tell me.
I'm sorry!
I didn't think he'd look out
for me like this, though.
I feel like I could really become
a first-class magician
with Professor Claude.
That's enough silliness.
Time for remedial lessons!
You aren't going home until
you catch twelve lophorns!
And if I can't?
You're staying overnight.
You monster!
I hear Castor Gemini skips your
classes and your classes only.
You know what happens
if he drops out, yes?
Principal...
Next episode: "Castor Gemini's Fate."
Are you getting fired?!
EPISODE 4
CASTOR GEMINI'S FATE
Help me out.
I'll give you pudding!